Marc F. Munic

mfmunic@gmail.com | 619-356-8642 | San Diego, CA

GitHub | LinkedIn | Portfolio

Fullstack Web Developer with a career ranging from the military to a wide variety of industries and roles. Experienced in React/Redux, Node, Mongo, and AWS (S3, Lambda, EC2, CodePipeline, Cognito, IAM). Spends free time continuing to learn new technology e.g. Unity/C# and React-Native.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- AWS
- React.is
- Redux
- Node.js
- Firebase
- Jasmine
- Jest
- AJAX

- Express.js
- NPM
- Git
- Github
- MongoDB
- HTML5
- CSS3
- Okta

- JavaScript
- JQuery
- Bootstrap
- MaterializeCSS
- AntD
- Go
- Robot
- Jira

APPLICATIONS BUILT

Forcepoint Explicit Proxy

- A proxy that goes between a user and a firewall, used to a layer of protection from cyber attacks.
- Utilized Go for actual proxy and Python Framework Robot for testing.

Forcepoint Login Page for platform access

- Created the login screen for the cloud software, it allowed customers and customer service access through different means.
- Customer's login is controlled by AWS cognito to ensure security, this was backed by extensive PEN testing.
- Customer Service could login as a customer, through 2FA, an Okta service that managed in-house signon, and then AWS cognito.
- UI utilized React; Backend utilized multiple AWS and Okta services.

Zeeto Experiment Manager Lab

- Middleware that directs users when clicking on ads to a client's website.
- Allows for A/B testing for different devices without changing the ad or it's metrics.
- Utilized Azure, AWS, Mongo, React/Redux, Node, and Jest.

Rock, Paper, Scissors, Lizard, Spock - https://mfmunic.github.io/rock-paper-scissors/

 Multiplayer game based on Rock Paper Scissors. Utilized Firebase to connect players moves and chat options

Marc F. Munic

mfmunic@gmail.com | 619-356-8642 | San Diego, CA

GitHub | LinkedIn | Portfolio

EDUCATION

• UCSD, San Diego, CA

April 2016 - October 2016

UCSD Coding Bootcamp - Full Stack Web Development

An intensive 24-week course dedicated to designing and building web applications.

• Ashford University, San Diego, CA

September 2010

B.A. Psychology

• Naval Nuclear Power Training Charleston, SC

September 2002

WORK EXPERIENCE

• Software Engineer II at Forcepoint

1/2019 - 06/2020

- Built UI for platform using React and introduced Redux
- Implemented Internationalization to platform
- Created seamless automation and use for login page
- o Built the explicit proxy system in Go

• Junior Software Engineer at Zeeto.IO

12/2017 - 12/2018

- Worked on Front End for main platform
- Built entire Router App from UI through AWS to two Databases
- Integrated Router App to Drupal for use in other services

• Admin at Mt. Soledad National Veterans Memorial

4/2016 -

11/2017

- Project Manager for Website and Mobile App
- Coordinate Veteran Honor Ceremonies with Donors and Trustees
- o Coordinate Major holiday events for Memorial day and Veterans Day
- o Maintain Database of plaques, membership, and donors.

• CEO at MANDR, Development, Inc.

1/2016 - 1/2019

• Buy, rehab, and sell single family homes

	buy, remue, and sen single running nomes	
•	Board Member at City Heights Town Council	10/2013 - 4/2017
•	Board Member at City Heights Area Planning Committee	4/2013 - 4/2017
•	Founder/Board Member at Exusmed	7/2013 - 5/2015
•	Campaign Manager/Consultant at Local San Diego Elections	10/2011-11/2014
•	Project Coordinator at Bridgepoint Education	1/2008 - 10/2010
•	Machinist Mate 3rd Class at US Navy	4/2002 - 4/2007